<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Orange County Scottish Rite News</title>
    <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Orange County Scottish Rite News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Commander of Kadosh</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/commander/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/commander/</guid>
      <description>Brethren,
It&amp;rsquo;s April - the darkness of winter is behind us and spring brings with it the promise of warmth and light. Let&amp;rsquo;s use this as a reminder that no matter how cold and dark things may seem, there will always be warmth and light ahead of us.
We are in a period of renewal - we are returning to our Lodge and, in so doing, we are positioned to renew our activities to support our Brethren and support our charity - The RiteCare Childhood Language Center of Orange County.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Director of the Work</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/director-of-the-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/director-of-the-work/</guid>
      <description>It’s that time of the year again… reunion time!
Given the extraordinary times we’ve all found ourselves in, we made the decision to join forces with a few of our fellow Valleys in Southern California for our next reunion. So on June 10th and 11th, our Valley will work with Long Beach (and hopefully a few others) to put on a great reunion for our new Scottish Rite Brothers!
While our long term goal is to hold our own reunions at least once a year, the current plan will be this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Secretary</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/general-secretary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/general-secretary/</guid>
      <description>Brethren:
Spring has arrived, and with that comes our Spring Reunion in early June. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t attended a Reunion recently, please make a point of seeing a degree or two. We will confirm the exact dates and all other info in the May newsletter.
After much consideration, input from Supreme and the leadership in our Valley, a recommendation to increase our annual dues will come to vote during our June stated meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of Kadosh</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/master-of-kadosh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/master-of-kadosh/</guid>
      <description>Greetings Brethren,
Here we are in a very pivotal moment in all of our lives. Some people are shedding the bad energy, laziness, and worry the pandemic has brought to our lives. Some of us are gearing up and getting back to the point we all left off at. Some of us are starting fresh changing our lives completely because the old habits just weren’t working out. However or whatever way you’re dealing with life now, just know that change can feel very uncomfortable and suspenseful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wise Master</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/wise-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-04/wise-master/</guid>
      <description>Greetings Brethren,
April is upon us and with that, we begin the second quarter of our Scottish Rite year. I like to take this time and reflect upon or renew the commitments made from our New Year’s Resolutions and if necessary, tweak or adjust as necessary. Personally, I have been chasing the same 15 pounds since college, promising to moderate my affection towards beer, drink less coke zero, and to read more regularly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
