<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Orange County Scottish Rite News</title>
    <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Orange County Scottish Rite News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-chaplain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-chaplain/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-clc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-clc/</guid>
      <description>Language Center Update Welcome back to the RiteCare Language Center of Orange County! We are very thankful for the new year and all the opportunity it brings to our children and families. We hope our friends at the ScottishRite Valley of Orange County will have a fantastic 2022!
Our families returned to the Childhood Language Center, Orange County in January after our winter break. As always we were prepared with updated COVID precautions which allow us to continue providing services for families who need in-person, face to face therapy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-commander/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-commander/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-general-secretary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-general-secretary/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/director-of-the-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/director-of-the-work/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Director of Masonic Education</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-masonic-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-masonic-education/</guid>
      <description>Master Craftsman Program As a reminder, Master Craftsman Study sessions are now being held on the second Monday of the month, from 5-6pm. As in the past, these sessions will take place via Zoom.
Venerable brother James Cervantes and I are here to answer any questions and guide you. If you have questions, please don’t hesitate to reach out to either of us by e-mail:
 Andrew Todd, 32° :. atodd@ocscottishrite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-editor/</guid>
      <description>From the Editor I’d like to express my thanks again to the heads of body for contributing their excellent and thoughtful articles this month and for doing so in a timely fashion.
Calling All Writers!  You don’t have to be a head of body or a member of the line to contribute to this newsletter! If you have something to say from a masonic perspective — perhaps insights into your masonic ruminations, scholarly endeavors you’d like to share, or general news for the brethren — this newsletter is your conduit for those ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master of Kadosh</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-master-of-kadosh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-master-of-kadosh/</guid>
      <description>Master of Kadosh Greetings brethren,
For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know me, my name is Cristian De Dios, member of Anaheim Lodge 207.
I believe this months news letter is about brotherhood. Well, I just had aquick self-reflective moment where I envisioned myself growing up and playing soccer, basketball, baseball, and Varsity Football. Ive always loved being part of a team of kids or guys coming together for the purpose of helping each other win, get stronger, be more confident, using strategy to overcome obstacles, or just having a cool place to hang out and laugh at each other&amp;rsquo;s oddness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Warden</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-senior-warden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-senior-warden/</guid>
      <description>Senior Warden Brotherly Love Happy February, brothers; the month of love, as it were. With Valentines Day sitting squarely in the middle of the year’s shortest month, it’s worth knowing that February 14th was chosen as St. Valentine’s Day — or the Feast of St. Valentine — not for any rosy associations, but because that was the date that the Catholic priest Valentine was set to be executed by Emperor Claudius II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venerable Master</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-venerable-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-venerable-master/</guid>
      <description>Venerable Master Hello my brothers and welcome to the new year and to the new line of officers for 2022. I am very honored to serve as the Venerable Master for this year and I am proud to be serving with all of the other officers.
This year we switched to a Zoom Officer Installation ceremony with a virtual Illustrious Frank Loui 33º SGIG as our Installation Officer. Illustrious Art Salazar 33º was virtually flawless as our Master of Ceremony.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wise Master</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-wise-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-02/2022-02-wise-master/</guid>
      <description>Wise Master Greetings Brethren,
Recently, my high school buddies and I started a podcast. We are all approaching 40 and thought: &amp;ldquo;Hmmm, x person knows football, y person knows litigation, z person knows technology and nth person, name your subject.&amp;rdquo; We&amp;rsquo;ll keep the topics light and the characters many, people will follow, maybe a few laughs. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what we were thinking and don&amp;rsquo;t worry, I won&amp;rsquo;t pedal it on you in this venerable space.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
