<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Issues on The Orange County Scottish Rite News</title>
    <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Issues on The Orange County Scottish Rite News</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/language-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/language-center/</guid>
      <description>Language Center News Welcome back to the RiteCare Childhood Language Center or Orange County! December is always a fun time to be in the clinic! The air is crispy the children are excited for Christmas, and the student clinicians are excited for their break (the supervisors are too). There is an energy that takes over this time of year that just cannot be match.
 This semester at the clinic has been a huge success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Director of Masonic Education</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/masonic-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/masonic-education/</guid>
      <description>Master Craftsman Program As a reminder, Master Craftsman Study sessions are now being held on the second Monday of the month, from 5-6pm. As in the past, these sessions will take place via Zoom.
Venerable brother James Cervantes and I are here to answer any questions and guide you. If you have questions, please don’t hesitate to reach out to either of us by e-mail:
 Andrew Todd, 32° :. atodd@ocscottishrite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Director of Ritual</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/director-of-ritual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/director-of-ritual/</guid>
      <description>Director of Ritual Joshua and Muhammad–A Masonic Duad In the Master Mason chapter of Morals and Dogma, Albert Pike warns about the dangers of hypocrisy and ambition. Pike says that the highest object of human ambition is to subjugate the will of others because it is the exercise of the highest power. He points out that this subjugation of the will is at the bottom of both proselytizing and propagandism, and gives the example of the Catholic Church for the former and the French Republic for the latter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor, Director of Masonic Education</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/editor/</guid>
      <description>From the Editor I’d like to express my thanks again to the heads of body for contributing their excellent and thoughtful articles this month and for doing so in a timely fashion.
Calling All Writers!  You don’t have to be a head of body or a member of the line to contribute to this newsletter! If you have something to say from a masonic perspective — perhaps insights into your masonic ruminations, scholarly endeavors you’d like to share, or general news for the brethren — this newsletter is your conduit for those ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Secretary</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/general-secretary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/general-secretary/</guid>
      <description>General Secretary Brethren: A very Happy New Year to all of the Brothers of the Orange County Valley. January is a busy month. We will be having our Stated Meeting on Monday, January 3rd at 6:30 pm at the DeMolay Center. Our Installation Ceremony for 2022 officers will be held at the Demolay Center on Sunday afternoon, January 16th. An email will be coming out with more information. Installation is one of the best ceremonies in the Scottish Rite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Representative of the Sovereign Grand Inspector General in California Orange County Scottish Rite Valley</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/personal-representative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/personal-representative/</guid>
      <description>Personal Representative Dear Brethren: On behalf of the Orange County Scottish Rite Valley, it is my pleasure to welcome you to a New Year, hoping that 2022 brings the promise for a return to a more normal program and along with that, the chance to partake on all the activities scheduled for this year.
First and foremost, I would like to begin by recognizing and thanking our 2021 officers for giving their time to our Valley and our fraternity, starting with Hon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Warden, Orange County Lodge of Perfection</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/senior-warden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/senior-warden/</guid>
      <description>Senior Warden Have you made your New Years Resolutions? I don’t usually make a list for myself but I feel like I need to make some changes so the first change is to make a list. Obviously the idea is to make a list of goals that will help to make me a better person, husband, father, friend, brother during this year. Basically the last two years were bad and I don’t want to keep treading water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Orange County Scottish Rite News</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/temp_index/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/temp_index/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venerable Master, Lodge of Perfection</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/venerable-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/venerable-master/</guid>
      <description>Venerable Master Greetings Brethren, I would like to take this moment to wish you a happy and prosperous New Year’s. May GOD Bless you and your family with many cherished memories, during this New Year’s that may last for generations to come.
It has been an Honor and privilege to serve our Orange County Valley Scottish Rite this year, as Venerable Master. This year did not start out like I imagined, with us still having to deal with the COVID restrictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wise Master Elect</title>
      <link>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/wise-master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://news.ocscottishrite.org/issues/2022-01/wise-master/</guid>
      <description>Wise Master Elect Greetings Brethren,
I am looking forward to a new Scottish Rite year as your Wise Master elect in the Chapter Rose Croix and am even more excited to have our own Venerable elect, David Frias to my immediate right up there in the East, such as we were a few years ago with him as Commander (Council of Kadosh) and myself as Master of Kadosh (Consistory). How comforting indeed to partner with him again (as well as the other head of bodies)!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
